[MARIN]
Kai.
[slurps]
Do I really need to say it?
You know how I feel.
[slurps]
I love you.
Let's go out!
[KAI]
Sorry.
[groans]
[KAI] Sorry.
[AYUMI] Double denied.
[MARIN]
But why?
Tell me!
-We'd be so good together!
-Took that well.
Guess sitting next to him
was more than she could handle.
[MARIN]
Date me!
-Kai! I'm begging you!
-[all gasp]
Go out with me!
♪
[sighs]
[AYUMI]
Just a nod?
♪
[UKA] That's the first time
I've ever seen someone confess.
And it was to him.
[YURU] So, when are you
asking Satoru out?
[AYUMI] What?
Uh, whenever it feels right?
[SHIRAISHI]
Well he's not gonna do it.
Too much of a man-child.
URK!
[gasps]
[UKA]
Is this a normal thing?
If you're in love with someone,
do you have to confess
those feelings to them?
Not if you're fine
with the way things are.
Keeping with the status quo.
[SHIRAISHI]
Marin's actually tough.
Oh, yeah?
I doubt most
people could do that.
If a boy in our class
rejected me, I think I'd die.
Awkward.
For real.
Friendships can end like that.
[TAO]
And one just did.
Freaky.
[STUDENT 11A]
Where did that wind come from?
[UKA] I haven't really
thought about it,
-but they're right.
-[wind whooshing]
I shouldn't tell
Miura how I feel.
SPARKLE 11 FEELINGS
BURST FREE
[MIRU] Yeah!
I'm crazy about any girl
in a fluffy sweater like this!
I wanna give her a hug!
[AYUMI]
What're those boys up to?
They're reading a fashion mag
and rating all the girls.
[YASUSHI] Man,
these girl are fit! So, Kai.
Which one's your type?
[UKA]
I wanna know too!
Tell us!
[YASUSHI]
Come on, man.
♪
[UKA]
Tell us!
-Her.
-[girls gasp]
[YASUSHI]
So, who's not your type?
[KAI]
Girls who reek of perfume.
Then, just to be clear,
girls like Marin?
Ugh!
Not true!
My perfume smells great,
thank you!
-Grrr!
-Eep!
[MARIN]
All right, Ishimori!
Uh-huh?
You don't understand
these things,
so don't talk about them!
You probably don't know
the first thing about
romance, anyway!
That's valid.
I wonder if Uka has a crush.
[GROUP]
Hm?
♪
[UKA] Well, he's sitting
right behind me.
So I should probably say no.
Yes, I do.
[SATORU]
Tell us, girl!
What's your type?
We've gotta know!
[UKA]
Careful, now.
-Him.
-[laughter]
That's opposite of Kai!
[MARIN]
Well, you can't stop there!
Do you prefer black hair,
or blond?
[groans]
Um.
Black hair.
♪
[MARIN] Of course!
Obviously!
Hey. I have good news!
[screams]
MY CURRENT ROAD
-Huh?
-[MARIN] Hi, hi!
[STUDENT 11A]
Heyo.
Ready to go?
[UKA]
What?
♪
See?
The spitting image
of your perfect man!
IDENTICAL
MARIN
[UKA]
Oh.
[evil laugh]
[UKA]
I'm sorry.
I've gotta go home.
[MARIN] If you don't go out
with this boy I found,
[echoing]
then I'll end you!
LOVE IS WAR
I WANT TO GO HOME
KARAOKE
[UKA]
This is unfortunate.
Hey, Kai!
I can check in
for all of us, so, scram!
Don't get the wrong idea!
I didn't wanna come here!
Okay?
It's just, Ishimori
wants a boyfriend!
[UKA] I can't believe
I'm here again.
Miura must think I'm weird.
No, I doubt he even cares.
[MARIN]
Well, let's go!
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
This is a bummer.
♪
[STUDENT 8B] Hold on.
Isn't that girl your stalker?
I told you,
you had the wrong idea.
Then she'd be your?
[sighs]
Stop talking.
-[STUDENT 8B] Aight.
-[door shuts]
[STUDENT 11B]
Testing!
Turn off the echo!
[STUDENT 11B]
You wanna eat?
[STUDENT 11C]
I could use a snack.
[UKA]
What am I doing here?
[STUDENT 11A] Marin,
that weirdo a friend of yours?
[MARIN]
Nah, just a classmate.
But she's trying
to get a boyfriend!
And one of you is exactly
who she's looking for!
[BOYS]
Ah, crap!
[STUDENT 11C] Who is it?
[UKA] I don't like any of them.
Oh, God!
Please not me!
Okay, Sueyoshi wins!
-Me?
-[UKA] No.
[MARIN]
He's just being shy, Ishimori.
Don't take what they're saying
too seriously.
-C'mon, tell him!
-[indistinct chatter]
"I'm way into you.
Go out with me."
But I...
"I"
I can't!
I'm not into Sueyoshi at all!
My type is a quiet, mature boy.
One who has a piercing
in each ear!
The kind of guy
who wears baggy shirts
and some torn-up pants
would be more for me.
That would be my type!
[whimpers]
A guy--
[gasps]
Like me?
You're off work?
[KAI]
And about to head home.
You comin'?
[AYUMI]
Friendships can end like that.
♪
"I"
I would love to.
[UKA] I'm not worried
about that anymore.
SHOPPING DISTRICT
[indistinct street chatter]
[UKA]
Thank you.
[KAI]
Sure.
[UKA] Um. I had no idea we'd be
going to your workplace.
[KAI]
Sure.
Who am I supposed to be to you?
[UKA] What kind of relationship
do we have?
Miura?
[KAI]
What up?
[UKA]
I want to know.
Who are you to me?
[indistinct street chatter]
If it's not weird...
[KAI]
Protector and protected.
It feels unique.
I hate trying to explain it
to other people.
So, then
you prefer black hair?
♪
I prefer blonde hair.
[chuckles]
Make up your mind!
It's become a habit,
protecting you.
♪
[UKA]
I get to be around him.
And that should be enough.
But still, I can't help
wanting more.
I never thought
this would happen to me,
but I promised.
I won't lie again.
[ABE]
Starting tomorrow,
we begin preparing
for field day!
[SATORU] Yeah! Let's show
everyone what we've got!
[AYAKA] Yeah,
our class is kinda only good
at the sporty stuff.
Why even bother?
[TAO]
The main event's relay.
-Wanna be in it, Ishimori?
-[UKA] Mhm.
[KIYOSHI] Come on,
quit jokin' around!
-[chuckles]
-What?
Ha. My girl, Uka,
rocks at sports!
And she's way faster than you!
[YASUSHI]
Believe it when I see it.
[chuckles]
FIELD
[panting]
[gasps]
Huh?
[YASUSHI, KIYOSHI]
Seven point five-eight seconds?
[KIYOSHI]
Holy crap, Ishimori!
Oh, thank you.
I doubt I'm the fastest,
though.
You better not hold back.
-I won't!
-[chuckles]
[TAO]
Well, it's settled, then.
[UKA]
I'll give field day my all.
But the real race
is still catching up to him.
And I'm trying!
[TAO] 'Kay, and you two
are gonna join her.
[YASUSHI, KIYOSHI]
Seriously?
[panting]
RELAY PRACTICE
[KIYOSHI]
Damn it!
[SHIRAISHI] When it's time
to pass the baton,
you need to pay attention
to your partner's speed
and the length of their stride.
[AYUMI] Right!
[TAO] Kiyoshi!
Pick up the pace!
[KIYOSHI]
Aye, aye!
[YURU] Kai should be
practicing with us,
since you'll be passing
the baton his way.
[KIYOSHI] Take it!
[AYUMI] Thanks!
[panting]
[UKA] Bummer that Miura
couldn't make it here.
Guess he must've gotten
too busy
with the cheer squad.
HUH?!
GOGGLE
[SHIRAISHI] I feel like you're
always talking about Kai,
don'tcha think, Ishimori?
[YURU]
The pupil admires her teacher!
[indistinct students chatter]
[SHIRAISHI] Hey, wait a sec!
Unless.
Could it be you're actually
into him that way?
Huh? Do tell!
Don't sweat it, girl.
[whimpers]
[UKA]
I can't deny it now!
[STUDENT 11D] So,
why're you still hangin'
with that basic girl?
[STUDENT 11E]
Don't you want a girlfriend?
As much as anyone else,
ya know?
Girls aren't gonna talk to you
while you're around her.
I don't think girls
are worried about that.
[slurps]
But the opposite's still true.
[STUDENT 11E]
How so?
Oh, no.
I can't practice.
[STUDENT 11D]
Think, my man.
With you there,
no one's ever gonna
try hitting on that
nerdy chick.
She probably wants
to find someone,
but she can't.
I mean, what freshman doesn't?
[sighs]
[UKA] Maybe
I'll use a ballpoint
to draw a light draft.
[KAI]
What are you doing with that?
♪
Took on more work again?
I wanted to!
Look at them all!
The shirts are so boring!
You should spend your time
drawing something
cute on all our shirts!
[chuckles]
[sighs]
I could draw something
on the back of yours, too!
So, uh, could you...
[screams]
No, no, no!
Not while I'm here!
I just, uh, wasn't ready!
Don't mind me.
I'm all right.
[whimpering]
[KAI]
You drawing everyone's?
Don't overload yourself.
[chuckles]
♪
Need any help?
[UKA]
Sure! Uh.
I need someone
to draw on mine, if you could!
[KAI]
No. Not a chance.
[UKA]
That's okay.
He's still keeping me company.
So, how much longer?
[UKA]
What?
[KAI] Are you going to be
like this all the way
until graduation, or what?
I'd say...no.
Yeah.
Got it.
♪
[UKA] That day when Miura
found me
and brought me to my new world,
I became very stubborn.
If I'm honest with myself,
maybe I've become
too greedy since then.
FIELD DAY
-[whistle blows]
-[students cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
Get ready!
The Hachimitsu field day
officially begins now!
HACHIMITSU FESTIVAL
[gunfires]
Attention all festival goers!
We found a lost child!
If you are missing a boy
in a blue hat named Sho,
come to the first-floor
entrance.
[gunfires]
[panting]
[indistinct chatter]
Huh?
Hm?
[SERINA]
Uka, you drew all these?
So cute!
Take a pic!
Wait.
But why is yours blank?
[AYUMI] She said it was no fun
drawing her own.
[YURU] Hey, turn around.
Lemme see!
[SERINA]
That sounds like her.
[YURU] I know you're happy
yours turned out cute,
right, Marin?
[groans]
She's not the kind of person
to ever hold a grudge,
so you could stand to be nicer.
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
Quit being so freakin' nice!
[grunts]
[AYUMI]
Huh?
[TAO] I'll be sure to give her
a piece of my mind pretty soon.
[SHIRAISHI]
You rock, Tao!
You're our knight
in shining armor!
Hm. And there.
"Honey Lemon Soda?"
[SERINA]
That's sweet!
Just like you!
What's with that bleach
blond hair?
Trying to be
the center of attention?
Nothing but a big ball of ego,
aren't ya, Miura?
[gasps]
[UKA]
What's happening?
-[gunfires]
-So, then?
Well, we've gotta do something.
Don't you worry.
Just focus on yourself today.
[UKA]
The time we spent together
should be enough.
But something feels off.
I want to help him.
[cheering]
[gunfires]
"I"
♪
[UKA]
I get it.
I lack confidence because
I get help more than I give it.
[AYUMI]
Are you okay, Uka?
[indistinct students chatter]
[gasps]
Oh. Yeah.
Hey!
Seen Kai?
[AYUMI]
He's not over here!
Probs asleep, bro!
[SATORU]
Well, he's running late!
The cheer squad needs him!
[UKA] Hold on.
I'll look for him!
[RED TEAM 11A]
Uh-oh!
[slurps]
Aw, ya gonna cry?
Are you okay?
[chuckles]
Let's head out.
Wait a sec!
Have any of you seen Miura?
[scoffs]
[RED TEAM 11B]
You're desperate. Chill.
[RED TEAM 11C] It sounds like
poor Miura's gone missing!
[laughs]
[UKA]
I know that key.
The storage room!
[panting]
♪
Miura!
Can you hear me?
Oh, come on.
I thought I told them
the lock was broken!
[grunting]
[door thuds]
Are you there, Miu...?
[gasps]
[flight whooshing]
[muffled groans]
You found me this time.
I owe you one.
It's annoying
how you can always tell
when something's wrong.
[UKA] I'll make sure
to always find you.
[KAI]
No matter what?
[UKA]
Yeah.
Even if I'm way up high?
Like you were,
up on your balcony?
I'll just sprout
some wings, eh?
I figured you knew!
I've got wings of my very own.
Look at the time!
Let's go!
[gasps]
THROB
[KAI]
You'll need those wings.
[UKA]
I'll be fine.
Remember?
The thing you said
after karaoke?
You are the protector,
and I'm the protected.
But we can switch it up
now and then.
You can ask me for help.
Okay?
No matter how small it may be.
My dreams are coming true.
Even if they're selfish
and out of focus.
[cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
You've waited long enough!
Let's get this started
with our all-star cheer squad!
♪
-Huh?
-How is he here?
[gunfires]
[ANNOUNCER 11A] To all
inter-school relay contestants!
Please gather now
at the entrance!
I got such a good picture
of the boys!
They look so cool!
It your fault
Miura's back in action?
You shouldn't have done that.
[grunts]
[RED TEAM 11A]
You know what?
Seems like we can use
you to hurt him.
He fought back against
us at first,
but gave up as soon
as we threatened
to take you instead.
Sounds like if we really
wanna mess with him,
you're the best way.
Go ahead and try.
Just leave him out of it.
That'll be fine with me.
Shut it.
You're not scared?
For real, girl.
Watch it.
We'll hurt you.
Go ahead.
It's okay.
Huh?
[gasps]
[cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 11A] The red team
managed to pass the baton
to number five!
White, blue,
and green are close behind!
Yellow brings up the rear!
And they have Ishimori
on their team?
Are they actually
trying to win?
Who put her on the team?
Guess we lost this.
[chuckles]
Uka! Queen!
-Uka is my queen!
-[UKA] Thanks!
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
The baton passes hands!
♪
"I"
[UKA]
I've been thinking a lot.
Or...maybe not at all.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
Look at her go!
-Yellow defies expectations...
-U-ka go!
U-ka go! - and kicks off
at lightning speed.
The gap with the blue team
is already closing!
[cheering]
[UKA] Whatever happens
to me, it's okay.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
She passed blue!
At the rate she's going,
they might manage
to get second place!
♪
[UKA]
I want to protect him.
♪
I can do it.
I will!
♪
I...
I'm hopelessly in love.
[gasps]
♪
[ANNOUNCER 11A] Yellow's
catching up to red, bit by bit!
And there!
Yellow has taken
the lead in a huge upset!
-[SHIRAISHI] You did it!
-That was incredible, Ishimori!
[TAO]
You closed a huge gap!
[AYUMI]
Ah. Huh?
Hey, Uka.
Who drew those things
on your back?
They're so cute!
[cheering]
Huh?
-[screams]
-[SHIRAISHI] Wrong place!
[cheering]
[KAI]
You'll need those wings.
[UKA]
I've got wings of my very own.
[cheering]
[sobs]
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
There you have it, folks!
In this year's
inter-school relay,
the yellow team wins!
[cheering]
Hey, Uka?
If Kai ever liked another girl,
do you think you'd be okay?
[UKA]
I would not.
Do you want to be with him?
[crying]
[UKA]
More than anything.
Then I'd say there's no reason
to hold those feelings
back anymore.
Now is the time.
Yeah?
Take the step.
Okay, Uka?
♪
[chuckles]
Hm?
[gasps]
[AYUMI] Right now?
[YURU] For real?
[flight whooshing]
[UKA]
What?
Am I dreaming?
Miura.
I love you.
I want to be yours.
Make me your girlfriend.
♪
Yeah.
This is definitely a dream.
♪
How else could this happen?
Could I ever be so lucky?
♪
TO BE CONTINUED